<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ICCCA</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>


    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_newactivity1">newactivity1</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
    <string name="home_text">\t \tThe evolution of computing and Communications Technologies and their reliability in the different areas of the industry has changed completely the design of automated systems. Computing covers application of Computer Science to the mathematical modeling of complex systems in the field of Engineering and Sciences. Computing is interdisciplinary and application oriented, focusing on techniques and tools that enable computational simulations to be performed.\n \tThe vision today is to best utilize the media of communication. Communication processes are fundamental part of virtually every aspect of human computer interaction (HCI). Research on HCI or data communication takes you to the cutting-edge of research and theory in all areas with in the field of communication like exploration of communication processes, antecedents and consequences of communication in a broad range of network communication.\n"</string>
    <string name="contect_us">\n <b>Dr. Parma Nand Astya</b> \n \n Professor and Dean. \n Plot no 2, Sector 17A, \n Yamuna Expressway\n  Greater Noida,Uttar Pradesh  Pin-201308, INDIA  Tel: +91120-4806897
        Mob: +91 9810446717</string>

    <string name="add">
        School of Computing Science and Engineering
Galgotias University, Plot no 2 Sector 17A,
Yamuna Expressway, Greater Noida, UP (INDIA) PIN-201308
www.galgotiasuniversity.edu.in , Phone: +91-120-4806897
</string>

    <string name="title1">Talk Title: "Communication Architectures and Systems for Smart Cities"</string>
    <string name="datat1">New advances in information and communication technologies allow cities to be efficient and smarter. Smart cities benefit the population through the offered services and applications. In order to gather the information, it is required a considerable amount of sensors connected through a sensor network. In this talk, we will review last advances in low cost sensors and sensor networks for Smart Cities. Moreover, we will show the communication architectures and protocols developed for Smart Cities. We will also review the most well-known artificial intelligence techniques for Smart cities. Finally, we will finish the talk showing some real applications. </string>
    <string name="name1">Prof. Jaime Lloret \nAssociate Professor, Polytechnic University of Valencia</string>
    <string name="data1">Prof.Jaime Lloret(jlloret@dcom.upv.es) received his M.Sc. in Physics in 1997, his M.Sc. in electronic Engineering in 2003 and his Ph.D. in telecommunication engineering (Dr.Ing.) in 2006.He is a Cisco Certified Network Professional Instructor. He worked as a network designer and administrator in several enterprises. He is currently Associate Professor in the Polytechnic University of Valencia. He is the Chair of the Integrated Management Coastal Research Institute (IGIC) and he is the head of the "Active and collaborative techniques and use of technologic resources in the education (EITACURTE)" Innovation Group. He is the director of the University Diploma “Redes y Comunicaciones de Ordenadores” and of the University Master "Digital Post Production". He has been Internet Technical Committee chair (IEEE Communications Society and Internet society) for the term 2013-2015.He has authored 22 book chapters and has more than 380 research papers published in national and international conferences, international journals (more than 140 with ISI ThomsonJCR). He has been the co-editor of 40 conference proceedings and guest editor of several international books and journals. He is editor-in-chief of the “Ad Hoc and Sensor Wireless Networks” (with ISI Thomson Impact Factor), the international journal "Networks Protocols and Algorithms",and the International Journal of Multimedia Communications, IARIA Journals Board Chair (8 Journals) and he is (or has been) associate editor of 46 international journals (16 of them with ISI Thomson Impact Factor). He has been involved in more than 400 Program committees of international conferences, and more than 150organization and steering committees. He leads many national and international projects. He is currently the chair of the Working Group of the Standard IEEE 1907.1. </string>

    <string name="title2">Talk Title: "Automation in Health Monitoring"</string>
    <string name="datat2">There is an astonishing increase in people with chronic diseases globally over the past decade. Every year, the healthcare cost of managing chronic diseases such as diabetes and Alzheimer Disease in North America, is estimated to be several billions. Similar to the global scenario, in Canada, there is an increase in elderly population and a heavy burden on healthcare cost. But there is also growing evidence that Information and Communication Technologies (ICT) can reduce healthcare cost and improve the patient care and the quality of life for people with chronic diseases. Loss of autonomy as people age presses the need for modern health monitoring technologies and ICT to support assisted living in their own home, so as to avoid expensive in-hospital care. Intelligent health monitoring systems have been able to provide any-time-any-where patient to physician Communication, remote emergency care, quick response and diagnosis, and secure medical data communication addressing privacy concerns and all issues related to the medical history of a patient. Current research is focused on producing proactive and preventive healthcare solutions to control healthcare cost. Tools that support automated flow of information from hospital to the patient side and vice versa are in-demand for intelligent health monitoring. Computing paradigms such as pervasive computing, ubiquitous computing, body area networks, wireless sensor networks, internet of things, cloud computing and artificial intelligence techniques play an important role in making these systems talk/communicate with one another under harsh conditions. While developing and implementing these automated health monitoring systems, challenges arise in data collection, assessing and analyzing in real-time and creating immediate reactive and visualization solutions based on the intelligence gathered from the data. In this talk, some of the research contributions made to address these challenges for automation and their solutions will be presented. </string>
    <string name="name2">Dr. Janet Light\nProfessor, Dept. of Computer Science University of New Brunswick, Canada</string>
    <string name="data2"></string>

    <string name="title4">Talk Title: ""</string>
    <string name="datat4">""</string>
    <string name="name4">Prof. SnehAnand\nIITD </string>
    <string name="data4">Prof. SnehAnand, was born on 2 August, 1949 in Shimla, Himachal. She graduated in Electrical Engineering from Punjab University, Patiala in 1970 and did her Masters (Control and Instrumentation) and Doctoral Research (Biomedical Engineering) at the Indian Institute of Technology, New Delhi, in 1972 and 1976 respectively. She has contributed her 43 years of her life to Indian Institute of Delhi. She optimally combines her Engineering training with biomedicine to bring in innovative concepts and give them a practical shape as products which benefit many people in need. Dr. Anand’s systematic holistic approach that is well directed towards manpower training, innovative research and technology development. Her principal achievements are in the areas of transducers and biosensors, reproductive bioengineering and rehabilitation Engineering. Addressing the problem of population control she demonstrated how Electrical Engineering principles could be applied to understand the physiology of reproduction and provide an electronic reversible fertility control device. Her multiple areas of research includes General Surgery, Neurology, Anesthesiology, Cancer, Health IT, Orthopedic, Patient Monitoring, Ophthalmology, Cardiology, Home care, Dermatology, Pediatrics, Imaging, Rehabilitation and Brain computer Interface. </string>

    <string name="title5">"Cognitive Computing"</string>
    <string name="datat5">"Cognitive Computing"</string>
    <string name="name5">Dr. Suneel Wattal\nIndustrialist </string>
    <string name="data5">An Engineering graduate from BITS, Pilani, with an MBA in Finance and Master in Computer Applications. Over 26 Years of industry experience in Delivering Optimal Results in High-growth Environments. Worked with State Bank of India, SQL Star, Polaris Software, Oracle, General Electric, Colt Telecom and IBM. Has built an expertise in Application development and consulting, working across Technologies and Functional domains. Performs in various roles across Consulting, Solutioning, Project and Programme Management. Has expertise in Delivery Management, Client relationships, Infrastructure support, Transitions and Skill management with in-depth experience in Energy, Telecom, Banking and Financial domains. Global exposure in the areas of Business Process Analysis, Software Development, System Integration, Vendor Management, Strategic Business Planning. Currently working in IBM as a Global Delivery Project Executive for a key US based customer, managing a team of resources, located across geographies. </string>

    <string name="title6">"Cloud Computing for Sustainable development"</string>
    <string name="datat6">Sustainable development means the idea that social, environmental, and economic progresses are all attainable within the limits of our earth’s natural resources. It approaches everything in the world as being connected through space, time and quality of life. Information and Communication Technologies (ICTs) are changing every day of our lives and it can help to bridge this gap and hence lead to a reduction in the level of poverty. The key note mainly, focuses on sustainable development through cloud computing and also discuss on the different types of services and applications of Cloud computing can be used as the tool for sustainable development and for betterment of our daily life. Finally, it covers some recommendations about energy efficiency and reduces the cost of the services as pay for use. </string>
    <string name="name6">Prof. Dr. Subarna Shakya\nTribhuvan University, Nepal </string>
    <string name="data6">Subarna Shakya holds Ph.D. in Computer Engineering from Lviv Polytechnic National University, Ukraine. He served as Executive Director at National Information technology Center, Government of Nepal and also head of Department of Electronics and Computer Engineering, Director of Center for Information Technology and Chairman of Electronics and Computer Engineering Subject Committee, Institute of Engineering, Tribhuvan University. He has also served as coordinator of EURECA (European Research and educational collaboration with Asia) and IDEAS (Innovation and Design for Euro-Asian Scholars). project is financed by the European Commission through the Erasmus Mundus Program .He is Professor of Computer Engineering at Department of Electronics and Computer Engineering , Pulchowk Campus, Institute of Engineering, Tribhuvan University also advisor member of National Information Technology Committee, Government of Nepal. He has published more than 70 technical and policy related papers in national as well as international reputed journals. He is steering committee member in School on Internet (SOI), Kieo University, Japan. He is presently serving as project coordinator of LEADER (Links in Europe and Asia for engineering, education, Enterprise and Research exchanges) financed by the European Commission through the Erasmus Mundus. He has delivered his key note speech in Seoul National University, South Korea and in the 16 International Multi Topic Conference (INMIC) 2013, 18 Dec 2013, Lahore, Pakistan organized by University of Engineering and Technology and IEEE and Invited Speaker in "e-Government Implementation in Nepal, 8 Oct 2012 at San Diego University, San Diego, USA as well as on "e-Government initiative and adopting Cloud computing as an e‐Government Platform in Nepal" 8 Oct 2014 at University of Nevada, Las Vegas, USA. He has given key note speech on "Implementing Cloud Service Models in e-Government at IEEE ICCCA, 29 April, 2016 at Galgotias University, India. He has also Invited Speaker in "the Cloud computing for e-Government Implementation” 3 Oct 2016 at Santa Clara University, Santa Clara, San Francisco , USA. He is the expert member of Board of studies in South Asian University, India. </string>


    <string name="title7">"High Performance Computing using OpenPOWER for Overcoming Moore's Law"</string>
    <string name="datat7">This talk will focus on enabling high-performance computing (HPC) in the current era where Moores Law seem to be hitting the wall again and again. Moores law is the observation that the number of transistors in an IC doubles approximately every two years. International Technology Roadmap for Semiconductors (ITRS) predicted in 2010 that growth would slow around 2013 and in 2015 Gordon Moore foresaw that the rate of progress would reach saturation. In view of these, today hardware has to be designed in a multi-core manner to keep up with Moores law. In turn, this also means that software has to be written in a multi-threaded manner to take full advantage of the hardware. The lecture will introduce the OpenPOWER technology that is poised to overcome the Moores Law and is well positioned for achieving the goals of HPC. The OpenPOWER Foundation is a consortium of research institutes, semiconductor companies and academic institutes to collaborate on POWER processor specifications, firmware and software. It was founded in 2013 as an open technical membership organization that will enable data centers to rethink their approach to technology. Members of the OpenPOWER Foundation are enabled to customize POWER CPU processors and system platforms for optimization and innovation for their business needs. These innovations include custom systems for large or warehouse scale data centers, workload acceleration through GPU, FPGA or advanced I/O, platform optimization for SW appliances, or advanced hardware technology exploitation. OpenPOWER enables research and business for futuristic supercomputers, hyperscale data centers and cloud computing platforms. Open collaboration enables OpenPOWER participants to share technologies and innovations with each other while taking advantages of open source software such as the Linux operating system. Well known OpenPOWER participants, out of over 250 members, include IBM, Google, Tyan, NVIDIA, Mellanox, Samsung, Xilinx, etc. Some of the participating research institutes are Jülich Research Centre, Oregon State University, Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory, Sandia National Laboratories, Tsinghua University, etc. India has many OpenPOWER partners, like IISc-Bangalore, IIT Bombay, IIT Roorkee, IIT Hyderabad, NIT Mangalore, NIT Warangal, IIIT Bombay, CDAC, Anna University, Coimbatore Institute of Technology, etc. OpenPOWER Research Facility (OPRF) has been established in Aug 2016 at IIT Bombay, to help drive the country’s National Knowledge Network initiative to interconnect all institutions of higher learning and research with a high-speed data communication network, facilitating knowledge sharing and collaborative research and innovation. Finally, the talk will introduce the solutions worked by many partners in the field of healthcare, eGovernance, defence, education, agriculture and high-performance computing</string>
    <string name="name7">Dr. Syed Saif Abrar\nSenior Corporate Advisor </string>
    <string name="data7">Syed Saif Abrar holds a Ph.D. related to System-level simulation and leads a team in IBM working on next-gen processors and systems. With more than 17 years of industry experience, he has contributed to compute systems ranging from tiny microcontrollers to high-performance architectures. His research interests include computer architectures, system-level design and modeling, performance analysis and IoT. In addition to corporate responsibilities, he is actively involved with academics institutes. He has driven many industry-academic projects and keenly shares his experiences and knowledge with the faculty and students. He has delivered talks in numerous international conferences and drives the IP activities in his organization. Further details are available in his LinkedIn profile: https://www.linkedin.com/in/saifabrar/ </string>

    <string name="title8">  </string>
    <string name="datat8">  </string>
    <string name="name8">Prof. P.K.Garg (Chief Guest)\nVice Chancellor , UTU Dehradun </string>
    <string name="data8">Prof. P.K. Garg, is currently serving as Vice Chancellor, Uttarakhand Technical University, Dehradun. He completed B.Tech (Civil Engg.) in 1980 and M.Tech (Civil Engg) in 1982 both from the University of Roorkee (now IIT Roorkee). He is a recipient of Gold Medal at IIT Roorkee to stand first during M.Tech programme, Commonwealth Scholarship Award for doing Ph.D. from University of Bristol (UK), and Commonwealth Fellowship Award to carry out post-doctoral research work at University of Reading (UK). He joined the Department of Civil Engg at IIT Roorkee in 1982, and gradually advancing his career rose to the position of Head of the Department in 2015. Dr Garg has shown extra-ordinary capabilities academically and administratively at various positions at IIT Roorkee. Prof. Garg has published more than 290 technical papers in national and international conferences and journals. He has undertaken 23 research projects and provided technical services to 83 consultancy projects on various aspects of Civil Engineering, generating funds for the Institute. He has authored a text book on Remote Sensing, and produced two technical films on Story of Mapping. He has developed several new courses and practical exercises in Geomatics Engineering. Besides, supervising a large number of undergraduate projects, he has guided about 70 M.Tech and 17 Ph.D. Thesis. He is instrumental in prestigious MHRD funded projects on e-learning; Development of Virtual Labs, Pedagogy and courses under NPTEL. He has served as experts on various national committees, including Ministry of Environment and Forest, EAEC Committee, NBA (AICTE) and Project Evaluation Committee, DST, New Delhi.</string>

    <string name="title3">Multi-objective Modelling and Optimization of Scientific and industrial application on Distributed computing infrastructures</string>
    <string name="datat3">The presentation is structured in four parts. It starts with an overview of the current research conducted by the applicant at the University of Innsbruck in the field of distributed and parallel systems. The second part introduces the ASKALON environment, the main research product of the applicant, designed to simplify and support the development cycle of scientific applications on distributed computing infrastructures. Afterwards, it presents a selection of the latest research methods and results obtained in two important areas: modelling, prediction and simulation of energy consumption and multi-objective optimization and scheduling of scientific applications on distributed computed infrastructures with respect to time, cost, energy, robustness and storage as simultaneous conflicting objectives. The third part of the talk presents the research conducted by the applicant in the area of industrial applications, with focus on massively multiplayer online gaming on distributed computing resources. The talk concludes with an outlook into the future research plans. </string>
    <string name="name3">Prof. Radu Prodan\nUniversity of Innsbruck, Austria</string>
    <string name="data3">Dr. Radu Prodan is Associate Professor in the Distributed and Parallel Systems group at the University of Innsbruck, Austria. He has over 20 years of research experience in the parallel and distributed computing areas. He earned his Ph.D. in 2004 from the Vienna University of Technology and his Habilitation degree in 2009 from the University of Innsbruck. Prof. Prodan has been involved in numerous national and international projects, including two Austrian-Indian cooperation project with Prof. Shajulin Benedict from St.Xaviers Catholic College of Engineering, Chunkankadai, Nagercoil and Prof. Neeraj Kumar from Thapar Institute of Engineering and Technology University, Patiala. Prof. Prodan authored over 150 conference and journal publications (including one IEEE best paper award) and one book in the areas of parallel and distributed computing. The IEEE Transactions on Cloud Computing journal ranked him recently as the 11th most productive researcher worldwide in the area of Cloud computing. </string>


    <string name="sponcer1">The conference organizers are seeking sponsors and industrial support for awarding exceptional contributions and offer the best stage for the event in terms of additional activities, such as invited speaker, invited panelists, best paper awards, gala dinner, and other social events.</string>

    <string name="name11">&lt;a href="https://github.com/storytellerr">link text1&lt;/a></string>
    <string name="title_activity_workshop_t">Workshop_t</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>

</resources>
