<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ICCCA</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>


    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_newactivity1">newactivity1</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
    <string name="home_text">\t \tThe evolution of computing and Communications Technologies and their reliability in the different areas of the industry has changed completely the design of automated systems. Computing covers application of Computer Science to the mathematical modeling of complex systems in the field of Engineering and Sciences. Computing is interdisciplinary and application oriented, focusing on techniques and tools that enable computational simulations to be performed.\n \tThe vision today is to best utilize the media of communication. Communication processes are fundamental part of virtually every aspect of human computer interaction (HCI). Research on HCI or data communication takes you to the cutting-edge of research and theory in all areas with in the field of communication like exploration of communication processes, antecedents and consequences of communication in a broad range of network communication.\n"</string>
    <string name="contect_us">\n <b>Dr. Parma Nand Astya</b> \n \n Professor and Dean. \n Plot no 2, Sector 17A, \n Yamuna Expressway\n  Greater Noida,Uttar Pradesh  Pin-201308, INDIA  Tel: +91120-4806897
        Mob: +91 9810446717</string>

    <string name="add">
        School of Computing Science and Engineering
Galgotias University, Plot no 2 Sector 17A,
Yamuna Expressway, Greater Noida, UP (INDIA) PIN-201308
www.galgotiasuniversity.edu.in , Phone: +91-120-4806897
</string>

<string name="title1">Talk Title: "Analytics - Journey from Data to Rich Insights".</string>
    <string name="datat1">Journey for any organization to become more of a data-driven organization provides an industrial perspective of data analytics. The process, methodologies, technology capability needed to convert the raw data to rich insights which can be used to support the strategic, financial, and operational decision making for better results for any firm will be discussed.0</string>
    <string name="name1">Prof. Anupam\nAccenture Digital based out of Dallas, Texas (USA)</string>
    <string name="data1">Anupam is a conscientious professional with astute business acumen with over 15 years of rich and insightful Leadership experience. During his career, he has worked with very prestigious organizations likes of IBM, Sears Holdings, SAS and Accenture. He is currently working for Accenture Digital based out of Dallas, Texas (USA) focusing on North American clients and moving back to India to take up a strategic key role with responsibilities around APAC and North American clients.</string>

    <string name="title2">Talk Title: "Integration of Cloud Computing and Wireless Sensor Network".</string>
    <string name="datat2">Wireless sensor network (WSN) is a base technology that is used to monitor remote areas in wireless modes with wide range of applications such as building health, fire alarms detection, traffic monitoring, pervasive healthcare etc. Whereas, Cloud computing is a model for enabling convenient, on demand network access to a shared pool of configurable computing resources (e.g., networks, servers, storage, applications, and services) that can be rapidly provisioned and released with minimal management effort or service provider interaction.</string>
    <string name="name2">Prof. S.C.Sharma\nIndian Institute of Technology Roorkee, India</string>
    <string name="data2">Professor S.C.Sharma (scs60fpt@iitr.ernet.in) received M.Sc.(Electronics), M. Tech. (Electronics and Communication Engg.) and Ph.D. (Electronics and Computer Engg.) in 1981, 1983 and 1992 respectively from IIT Roorkee (erstwhile University of Roorkee). He started his career as R and D Engineer in 1983 then joined teaching profession in Jan. 1984 at IIT-Roorkee and continuing till date. He has published over two hundred twenty research papers in national and international journals(107)/conferences(115) and supervised more than 30 projects/dissertation of PG students.</string>

    <string name="title3">Talk Title: "Big Data Analytics: Current Challenges".</string>
    <string name="datat3">Generating, storing and accessing terabytes or evenexabytes of data in real-time or near real-time is no more a challenge today. However, the key challenge faced today in exploiting big data to its true potential stems from the complexity and heterogeneity of the data itself – which not only poses algorithmic challenges to traditional machine learning research but also opens up a plethora of problems to those who analyze and derive insights from this vast ocean of data.</string>
    <string name="name3">Prof. Lipika Dey\nPrincipal Scientist at TCS Research and Innovation, India</string>
    <string name="data3">Dr. Lipika Dey is a Principal Scientist at TCS Research and Innovation, India. Her research interests are in the areas of noisy text analytics, machine learning and semantic search.Lipika has a Ph.D. in Computer Science and Engineering from IIT Kharagpur. Prior to joining Tata Consultancy Services in 2007, she was a faculty member in the Department of Mathematics at Indian Institute of Technology, Delhi from 1995 to 2006.</string>

    <string name="title4">Talk Title: "Artificial Neural Networks - Bio Inspired Modeling and Optimization Tool".</string>
    <string name="datat4">Neural networks are widely used as an alternative whenthe traditional mathematical models fail to simulate complex patterns. The simplicity of their implementation makes them appropriate for modeling and optimization of various complicated processes. The motivation behind neural computing is the possibility of creating an artificial computing network similar to the brain and nerve cells in our body.</string>
    <string name="name4">Prof. B.V Babu\nVice-Chancellor Galgotias University, India</string>
    <string name="data4">An acknowledged researcher and renowned academician, Dr B V Babu has 31 years of teaching, research, consultancy, and administrative experience. He did his PhD from IIT Bombay. He is currently the Vice Chancellor ofGalgotias University, Greater Noida (since May 2014). He also received ‘MTC Global Award for Excellence -2015’ and felicitation for being one of the ‘Top 10 Thinkers-2015- Indian Ranking’. He is also the recipient of ‘Best Paper Awards’ in CHEMCON-2000 and CHEMCON-2001 for the papers he presented at the International Symposia and Annual Sessions of Indian Institute of Chemical Engineers (IIChE).</string>

    <string name="title5">Talk Title: "".</string>
    <string name="datat5">\n\n</string>
    <string name="name5">Prof. M.S.Manna\nDirector, All India Council for Technical Education (AICTE)</string>
    <string name="data5">Dr. Manpreet Singh Manna, born on 14th March, 1971 at Patiala, Punjab (India), graduated in Electrical and Electronics Engineering from Mysore University, Mysore in the year 1993. He did his Master of Engineering in Power and Machines from Thapar University, Patiala and Ph.D. in Electrical and Instrumentation Engineering from SLIET (A Centrally Funded Deemed University established by Govt. of India), Longowal. Starting his teaching profession as Lecturer from SLIET in the year 1997, he has now attained the position of Director, All India Council for Technical Education (AICTE) under Ministry of HRD, Govt. of India, and New Delhi presently on deputation.</string>

    <string name="title6">Talk Title: "".</string>
    <string name="datat6">\n\n</string>
    <string name="name6">Prof. D.S.Yadav\nDirector, Government Engineering College Banda, India</string>
    <string name="data6">Prof. D. S. Yadav joined as First Director of Government Engineering College, Banda on 21 January 2015. Before taking this assignment, he was Pro. Vice Chancellor of Dr. A.P.J. Abdul Kalam Technical University, U.P., Lucknow during March 2013- Nov 2014. Earlier, he was at South Asian University, New Delhi, an international university established by South Asian Association for Regional Cooperation (SAARC) nations, where he was Chairperson of the Department of Computer Science at Faculty of Mathematics and Computer Science (2011-2013).</string>

    <string name="title7">Talk Title: "Internet of Thing: Applications, Future and Challenges".</string>
    <string name="datat7">The Internet of Things is emerging as the third wave in the development of the Internet. Internet of things (IoT) is expected to have a massive impact on consumer products, business and wider culture. The Internet will continue to become ever more central to everyday life and work, but there is a new but complementary vision for an Internet of Things (IoT), which will connect billions of objects – ‘things’ like sensors, monitors, and RFID devices – to the Internet at a scale that far outstrips use of the Internet as we know it, and will have enormous social and economic implications.</string>
    <string name="name7">Prof. Md Asri Ngadi\nProf. at UniversitiTeknologi, Malaysia</string>
    <string name="data7">Md Asri Ngadi is a member of IEEE and ACM. He completed his Master at the UniversitiTeknologi Malaysia and Ph.D. in Computer Science from Aston University, Birmingham UK with a study of networking protocols and security. Upon returning to Malaysia, he was appointed as the lecturer in Computer Science, and now he is appointed as Associate Professor at UniversitiTeknologi Malaysia. From 2005 till now, he leads many governments, international and industrial projects which developing secure protocols in many networking fields with total RM3.3 millions. He published more than 150 research work in various International Journals and International Conferences. Until now, he is supervising 10 Ph.D. students, and 10 are supervised till now.</string>

    <string name="title8">Talk Title: "Implementing Cloud service models in e-Government". </string>
    <string name="datat8">e-Government is the use of Information and Communication Technologies (ICTs) by government agencies to manage governance efficient and effective, and makes government more accessible and accountable to the citizens. The recent trends of this technology access by citizen and organizations bring expectations and demands on government.</string>
    <string name="name8">Prof. Subarna Shakya\nProfessor, Tribhuvan University, Nepal, Former Executive Director NITC, Nepal.</string>
    <string name="data8">Subarna Shakya holds Ph.D. in Computer Engineering from Lviv Polytechnic National University, Ukraine. He served as Executive Director at National Information technology Center, Government of Nepal and also head of Department of Electronics and Computer Engineering, Director of Center for Information Technology and Chairman of Electronics and Computer Engineering Subject Committee, Institute of Engineering, Tribhuvan University. He also served as coordinator, the IDEAS (Innovation and design for euro-Asian scholars project is financed by the European Commission through the Erasmus Mundus Action 2 Program .</string>


    <string name="sponcer1">The conference organizers are seeking sponsors and industrial support for awarding exceptional contributions and offer the best stage for the event in terms of additional activities, such as invited speaker, invited panelists, best paper awards, gala dinner, and other social events.</string>

    <string name="name11">&lt;a href="https://github.com/storytellerr">link text1&lt;/a></string>
</resources>
